//creating an array and passing the number , questions, options and answers

let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: 'How many moons does Saturn have',
        answer: '83',
        options:[
            '4',
            '100',
            '83',
            '72'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: 'Which planet is the biggest in our solar system?',
        answer: 'Jupiter',
        options:[
            'Pluto',
            'Mars',
            'Venus',
            'Jupiter'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: 'In order of their distances from the Sun, which of the following planets lie between Mars and Uranus??',
        answer: 'Jupiter and Saturn',
        options:[
            'Earth and Jupiter',
            'Jupiter and Saturn',
            'Saturn and Earth',
            'Saturn and Neptune'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: 'Which planet is known as the "Watery Planet" ?',
        answer: 'Earth',
        options:[
            'Mercury',
            'Earth',
            'Mars',
            'Jupiter'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: 'Which of the following is indicated by the colour of a star?',
        answer: 'Temperature',
        options:[
            'Weight',
            'Distance',
            'Temperature',
            'Size'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: 'Milky Way Galaxy was first seen by ?',
        answer: 'Galileo',
        options:[
            'Galileo',
            'Newton',
            'Marconi',
            'Martin Schmidt'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: 'The radiant energy of the sun is transmitted in the form of ?',
        answer: 'Short Waves',
        options:[
            'Short Waves',
            'Long Waves',
            'Particles',
            'None of these'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: '“Sirius”, the brightest star outside of the Solar System, is also called ?',
        answer: 'Dog Star',
        options:[
            'Cat Star',
            'Dog Star',
            'Fox Star',
            'Lion Star'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: 'The mass of Jupiter is almost',
        answer: 'One Thousandth of the mass of the Sun',
        options:[
            'Tenth of the mass of the Sun',
            'One Thousandth of the mass of the Sun',
            'Hundred of the mass of the Sun',
            'Half of the mass of the Sun'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: 'The darkest part of the shadow during eclipse is ?',
        answer: 'Umbra',
        options:[
            'Halo',
            'Umbra',
            'Penumbra',
            ' Black Hole'
        ]
    },
];